<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-06-09T17:43:55-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Your awesome title</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Welcome to Jekyll!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2019/06/09/welcome-to-jekyll.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to Jekyll!" /><published>2019-06-09T17:07:25-04:00</published><updated>2019-06-09T17:07:25-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2019/06/09/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2019/06/09/welcome-to-jekyll.html">&lt;p&gt;You’ll find this post in your &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll serve&lt;/code&gt;, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add new posts, simply add a file in the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory that follows the convention &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;YYYY-MM-DD-name-of-post.ext&lt;/code&gt; and includes the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;'Tom'&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints 'Hi, Tom' to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/docs/home&quot;&gt;Jekyll docs&lt;/a&gt; for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll&quot;&gt;Jekyll’s GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;. If you have questions, you can ask them on &lt;a href=&quot;https://talk.jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll Talk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">You’ll find this post in your _posts directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run jekyll serve, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">First Post Be Gentle</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/06/09/first-post-be-gentle.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="First Post Be Gentle" /><published>2019-06-09T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2019-06-09T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/06/09/first-post-be-gentle</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/06/09/first-post-be-gentle.html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;journal&quot;&gt;Journal&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This page is meant more of a journal than anything else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was inspired to start it up by a recent blog post of my old coworker Evan (https://irarelypostanything.tumblr.com/) on how writing has helped him think things through, as well as the now double UFC champ Henry Cejudo (lol).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Henry was the youngest olympic wrestling gold medalist, and then went on to become a MMA champion, recently fighting through a sprained ankle and coming back from being dominated at the beginning of the fight. One of the commentators, Daniel Cormier, remarked that for someone to accomplish so much they have to constantly be setting goals. Win a gold medal, get into UFC. Become UFC champion, win another championchip at a different weight class.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thinking about it, I realized that I didn’t really have any concrete goals that I wanted to work towards. I think this tends to lend itself to stagnation, and as a naturally lazy person I need some real motivation in order to even leave the house, let alone do anything mentally taxing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;thinking in real time&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
So what kind of goals do I want to set? I want them to be acheivable by myself, and should be able to be accomplished in a few months at the most. I don’t really care about progressing at work, so nothing on that front. Instead I’ll focus on things I do in my spare time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;okay&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1.) Be able to do the splits
	- I have very poor flexibility in my hips/legs due to sitting down my entire life- this is primarily motivated by wanting to improve my guard play in BJJ
2.) Squat 225
	- I’ve had this goal before and never lifted consistently enough to acheive it
3.) Paint my Warhammer 40k models!
	- I started back up my Word Bearers army and I’ve been too lazy to get them all painted up&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think these are some reasonable goals to start out with- hopefully there will be some blog updates showing some progress, but in any case I plan to flesh out some thoughts on other topics. Lets see :)&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Journal</summary></entry></feed>